so if you remember what I was trying to
explain yesterday and failed to explain
I'm just gonna demonstrate that to you
now so I found this yesterday and the
way I understand this is so we're
upstairs right now you just saw me walk
up some stairs so if you were to imagine
what is what would be exactly below
where I'm standing right now and I
worked it out it's roughly the area
where you have the big screen with the
windmill and so I think so this this I
think is a camera and the fyah
walk in this direction this is roughly
where the windmill would be why there
isn't actually a windmill here I don't
know it looks sort of like a placeholder
for it yeah I think my understanding is
correct
it's just I'm missing something okay
that's it