all right so now we're going to look at
what's over here which I forgot about
this what's that think I have to put
something there
what
Oh
you
okay
all right okay
just flat-out full game I'm playing
or mine
I don't think I'm supposed to do that
yeah yeah I reset it okay try that again
sterilizes way
I think that's wrong
or a different something in there
yeah it turned out I just had to wait
but I had to wait a while so this is
cleared out I guess so what's in here
okay alright let's try another one I
guess so I just did it again I put in
another one of these and I just let it
go
and it and the room rumbles for a while
but then it just stops kind of abruptly
so we have here now yeah
yeah so it seems like I put in one of
these faces and it gives me a room with
a guy that's a kid sitting on the bed
and like a different pattern on the
floor and the walls and the same here so
it seems like there are many
combinations of these faces so if I were
to guess these rooms are because there's
not much variation between these rooms
they're probably generated in some way
and so I'll try a few more every time I
put in one of these I have to wait for
like ten minutes so I'm not going to try
too many of them
yeah here's another one
and here's another
yeah
so anything look familiar here yeah yeah
so probably we're supposed to try these
out put in these faces and see what we
get so start with this one
so this is a room corresponding to the
face on the grave stones
not sure what that is on the right
alright gonna try the other one now I
guess nothing nothing to see here the
beds empty
here's the other room and it looks like
there's something here
unless you what to say about that
but I'm wondering now because the note
remember the note that came with this
game it said for you it was for you and
this note is referring to the player
it's saying you and I was already
thinking this but it seems like it's
possible this game was made for well
this part of the game was made for
somebody see like or at least at some
point it was it was a I don't know I
don't know it just seems like there is
is intended for somebody not me
certainly
okay we're still not done because we
still have whatever is over here or not
okay so okay I'll just end this here
then