[Music]
you
that's kind of fun actually going
through a for our video and noticing
that on one half of the video the window
is going in one direction and and the
other half it's going in the other
direction and pinpointing where the
change occurred and is this that's
neat
well that's red now oh yeah I was going
to mention this actually in a another
video I've come up here before and seen
it I've seen the camera at this height
before I don't know what causes it to
happen but sometimes I just come up here
and it's at this height it makes sense
in this case I think is that the
character was like right up at the
camera here and it seems to be like at
this level well this is still here oh my
god nothing else okay come on
Oh
uh-uh
I was the only one who still wanted to
put him down
what of what have I just walked into
that's it yeah okay okay so I actually
this is this is new to me I had seen
this yeah so I tried going down here
before but I think actually that was
before I even put in the code so I just
discovered this just now but you know
what I think actually this I think I
know what this is this is our a/b NLM
you recognize the shape of this one now
you help so I don't know what this is
here though yeah so I didn't imagine you
could catch this I mean oh I walked into
it
nothing happened
I'm covering a lot of interesting things
but I meant to talk about this because
this doesn't do anything right this menu
option nothing happens I'm guessing at
some point you could one of your pets
but uh well it's just like suggestions
or something yeah yes so well showing of
it that doesn't do anything
well Wow all right
you
this game is trying very hard to make it
seem like like there's an entity in it
like a ghost or an AI trying to
communicate with me it's interesting but
you know the way you know that there's a
ghost in a game trying to communicate
with you is if it comes out if it stops
being distant and it comes out and you
can have a you know a real time back and
forth with it and it stops being so
one-way like I I leave my PlayStation
and it comes comes out and does this
whole pre-recorded thing and well the
closest thing that's happened to that is
last video you know it actually answers
my questions but you know it only
responded to two of my questions and the
first one the first question I asked I
didn't even answer that question so no
obvious interactivity happening you know
then it answered the second question but
that could have been a coincidence yeah
so uh not entirely convincing yet but
you know looking forward to what I might
see next is very interesting this game
because you couldn't walk around and
something will just happen you know if I
created a new file and I tried to be
scientific about it I went I went and
did all the same things that I did this
time and the same things did not happen
none of the things happen none of the
oddities occurred like the thick of the
mirror room for example so there's a bit
of randomness in it and it's interesting
how it doesn't seem to really care
if you see everything I guess yeah so
it's interesting
you