you
hey so the door opened on its own I was
just in the other room for a couple of
minutes and I came back and the door was
open and I checked the recording because
I was recording and the door just opens
on its own I didn't do anything
so I'll take it right so I'm going to
show you what's in here now I haven't
seen it yet so this could be interesting
what is this a B n LM okay nothing
sorry for not talking very much I'm a
little bewildered on know the truth is a
little more than I was expecting to see
that's a dead kid yep yep okay wait
[Music]
okay wait I don't know so when I first
came down here I thought I was just
going to see like one room like
something but not this guy go in here I
can
Oh what
Oh
[Music]
all right so it's been like two minutes
and when those sounds are playing there
was nothing happening as far as I could
tell and nothing has happened since so
I'm just going to keep going there's
already been stuff that I could dig a
little deeper into and I'm going to do
that and keep you updated but also when
you come home next month hopefully
you're feeling a little more
enthusiastic about that now we can
investigate this together and maybe
you'll find stuff that I can't find here
Oh what the [ __ ] wait a second
what was that just now
can I get that to happen again
wait
I had to look at that for a moment
in the video I was a little nervous the
tones I think this is the same tones
that you might have heard in the
beginning I'm going to put in the
beginning the part where the door opened
and also the way the guy on the other
side was moving for a moment I'm going
to ask for your comment later on that so
I was looking around here so this is
backwards it says do you remember being
born and this just says Twitter's room
so interestingly I'm on the reverse side
here yeah okay so moving on
and I'm back up here again this again
okay I'm not going to do that right now
all right so I'm going to stop this now
actually