all right so I spent a while with this
just asking as many questions as I could
think of mostly like short three words
aims and most of the questions that I
asked just produced no answer or the
fall answer a default answer which is I
don't know most of them just gave me
that except for four of them and I'm
going to go through each of those four
now the first of the four was who is
tiara and the capitalization does not
make a difference who is tiara I also
tried who is care who is Mike who is
Michael and I tried other forms to like
just care just Mike just Michael this is
the only one that gave me anything
next one that I tried oh yeah
next I asked where am I
and then I asked who are you I don't
know why that just happened yeah so I
was saying who-who are you yeah I don't
know why that has changed color out of
nowhere
I think it broke II yeah I don't think
that even just just registered at all or
okay so that's not that's not what it
said before when I put in that question
did not look anything like that
interesting okay what what do I ask now
why why turn off I'll try just why okay
oh boy
you
yeah what the
this game this game okay all
right what away well I have to ask now
and to switch back again I think it just
okay I don't
so if I if I put in oh is it
put in who are you again is that going
to let me see what happens when I put
that in again
yeah so that's what it said originally
when I put it in oh well okay that's
bizarre so I guess I'm going to wait for
that to happen again
but I guess I'm going to end the video
now though
you