you
[Music]
oh hi there
that might be it
subways okay
so we might know who Marvin is now all I
need to be quick about this actually
because I could turn red again so I'm
going to ask who are you which I feel
like we know at this point but good to
confirm
talking about the house again it's
interesting but it is not an answer to
my question it not at all so what do you
think that means okay I should so yeah
so now I'm going to ask the other
question but do you remember being born
oh yeah it's just remember being born
because the whole thing does not fit
machine beyond school basement stairway
not also not an answer to my question uh
yeah and it was yeah well
well there you go okay I guess I'm an
idiot
I want to try that I guess I mean these
are people right there's my work so if I
walk over here okay so that's another
thing
anything out of the ordinary here it's
on the floor looks like a gift box and
stars and something else and anything
down here as usual no so this if you're
wondering what I'm doing here this is
Mike's face but without the eyebrows and
why am i doing that
well because eyebrows seem to be
important that's really it but nothing
seems to have actually it seems like
it's just right one just regular room
right yeah okay
I don't know because that's it I have
one more thing to try though
this one is care with eyebrows
so this is care with eyebrows
I put Mike's eyebrows on her
I could have other eyebrows on her but I
didn't on foot Mike Center I don't know
if this I I can't tell I can't tell if
it recognized it or not because
everything looks like any other room
this here it puts this
I don't know maybe that's just something
that it puts in any room
you