signs along the way that I ignored did
say what a completely ridiculous idea to
me but when I found my room
it made well I was shocked at first but
it made sense especially considering
where I found the game in the first
place that would be tied in some way to
me through you trying to think when was
the last time I saw any of you at all it
had to have been like 1999 I was a kid I
was a small kid tiny kid and after that
just you know it would make sense in the
timeline it's hard to do this while I'm
talking that's why I'm so quiet right
now
so if you're wondering what I'm doing
right now I have a drawing that I could
scan and send to you I just came home
and drew this big drawing and it still
you still need an explanation on because
they thought the drawing is not very
clear what scribbles really but um but
you need the visual to understand the
explanation alright so you need both I'm
about 90% sure this is gonna work and
10% not so sure but mostly sure
okay wait what do you think it is all
wrong again holy holy it works
I mean I was 90% sure but it's a little
shocking that it actually worked
that's very neat all right so the way
this works I'm supposed to pass on this
one
there it is okay okay so this one we
want to what we want to when asked about
the house so we're gonna ask clear just
where his house
okay um so I don't I don't know I I mean
this probably say asked me to go this
way right yeah I think that's what's
happening that's not what I was
expecting actually I guess a a road
makes sense but it's not visually the
same thing that I was expecting to see
see what the camera just did there it's
a frozen house I think we found the
house just found the house
from the house like he's still what what
you can't open it
I joked about I can't open doors
you
clockwise the top is going to right and
then you know the bottom is going to the
left right and so once you wanted to say
righty-tighty lefty-loosey or you know
you turn this turn this thing to the to
the right and I mean I still get
confused about that because I mean
though I know it's always the top but I
still have to think I have to think what
we have the door open now so I mean okay
all right okay it's interesting that
people appearing and disappearing
calendars here
[Music]
so these are different years this green
here starts off like checkerboard and
whatever this is and then weekends it's
green every day oh okay I don't know if
you got that immediately yes June to
November mm-hmm yeah on that topic I
don't remember meeting this girl at all
I don't remember knowing her at any
point I remember you saying that we were
that we we are exactly the same age I
don't I just don't remember even hearing
about anyone going missing all right I
don't have a single remember her going
missing or anything like that I mean I
was a kid but even then it could've been
one of those periods when we weren't
visiting very much but she's weird right
because no if you can you can verify
these dates but fifth of June 10th of
November
right when she went missing and when she
was found right and the 25th year I'm
wondering what the what the animation
means there right now the number is
animating a bit because right the 25th
of December on both calendars but
they're different years so I don't know
if it means it's the 25th of December in
this house but then it's two different
years so that's do agree there's a
resemblance very strong resemblance
between us what the hell that was an
experience
you
[Music]
Wow
what hell that was an experience
huh hey I could have sworn I just saw
above the bathtub
those white blocks with the symbols on
them you were seeing some of those
before I could have sworn I just saw one
of those right right there
yeah everything's different now tree is
gone
got a bucket here what's going on and
that looks the same
hmm
[Music]
fifth I don't know if I can find out the
in-game time and what the hell is this
[Music]
another care can I get on this bed I'm
supposed to get up on the bed don't know
how this is supposed to work yeah I
don't know I don't know you can do here
but you want to see something more free
no that's good I'm interested in this
window I don't really know what to do
but we could
come in through the window I don't know
if that's the thing yeah I don't know
there's something I missed in here I
don't think so that's a fun thing fun
thing that just happened I didn't do
that
um I can't closed doors I can't I can't
open doors either so I also can't yeah
that's fun I don't know I mean I I know
it I know what it wants me to do now
[Music]
Oh put everything back where it was
I still can't write so I said well
where did he just come from bathroom I
was gonna because he came from the
window as I was saying
yeah and then there's a cute little
ladder there
[Music]
I saw him at a birthday party once kids
are down the basement playing video
games
he's down thank you
he's older interesting
check your bathroom
[Music]
you
[Laughter]