[Music]
you
all right so this is just to prove to
you because I'm not lying about this I'm
gonna walk you through everything that
I've seen so far and obviously to be
exactly as I described it because this
is it and the first level is over here
I'm just going to keep going to right
here so you can see that the game is
apparently unfinished because there's
nothing over here so I'm just going to
show you the one and only level this
actually it's not the interesting part
but I'm just going to show you I'm going
to walk you through all this so you can
see that this is exactly what I
described
[Music]
first pets in this room and first thing
you got to do here is let her out of a
cage she just moves by the other one and
then you do that take the mama here
and then actually go over here and just
does that but if you do this if you lock
yourself in here that is run over there
[Music]
so once you're in here actually you can
find a little place here to walk to the
other side that's that and so there's
actually this another over here I can't
catch this one I've tried this is always
what happens so I don't know what's up
with that one so actually actually show
you the pause menu but here you can see
all the pets that you
[Music]
collected we've caught all right so
second one here is sort of music one the
idea here is you have to get your phone
over there to overlap with it and I'll
just cut to the chase you just set this
to what is it seventh and like that -
let me get that one all right so this
one's kind of interesting so the idea is
you weren't over here to catch a flower
here then you let's get rained on what
you're supposed to do is whenever the
flower comes over here you notice always
comes to the exact spot over there which
you can get this okay
that exact five
that's a spot yeah then the and that
happens and you'll be just catching boat
that way so yeah that's it for the
actual that's everything it's every
single pet here that I've been able to
catch so now we're going to show you the
part that's actually interesting
all right so I still can't catch this
guy the reason we're here is because in
the note that came with this which is
short the first line and all capital
letters I'm going to read it it says I
walked down stairs and when I got to the
bottom instead of proceeding
I turned the right and became a shadow
monster man though that a date June 13
1997 for you : please go to my website
on the sticker and also go to Cronus
room and press Start and press down down
down down down right start so I happen
to know this is run on strim because it
works so I go here I'm just going to do
this now why is it down down down down
down right sorry
alright so you can see that it accepted
it and the music stopped I'm just going
to go out this way here so uh it appears
to be the same except and actually leave
here it'll be a little bit different
alright so there's nothing out here as
far as I've seen but actually I think
there is something out here I just
haven't seen again
because it sure seems like and there's
no here sure seems like right I'm
supposed to come out here and look at
something I haven't found anything yet
but I'm thinking if I just keep walking
around here I'm going to find something
eventually I say
hey so I was talking about who I
couldn't find anything out here well I
just found this and last time I came out
here I was walking around in this space
here for over an hour and this time I
find this in less than 15 minutes so
this is just luck that I happen to find
this and I think if I were to restart my
console right now I would not be able to
find this again probably because I don't
remember what I what I did you know all
the directions that I went so so I'm
kind of scared to you know I want to
keep the console on until I figure this
out the situation is that I cannot open
this door I probably can't open the door
but I don't know what to do so I thought
I would just slip this in at the end if
you think you saw something that might
provide a clue please let me know all
right that's it