[Music]
you
I can't just wait thankfully I have been
suddenly inspired by an idea that is in
a way similar to the idea that brought
me to this house because that idea
involved pretending pretending something
was there that wasn't there and this
idea involves pretending that this door
right here this one it is open rather
than closed you can see that it's closed
but what I'm going to do and what I
invite you to do as well is picture I'm
going to picture in my head that this
door is actually open right now and if I
were to pass through this doorway what
would happen I would would I bump into a
door no because the door is open right I
would just keep going into the room
that's there and I happen to know I'm
gonna walk into the room right now that
I'm in the room I happen to know what
this room looks like because I saw in a
demo recording just today and you can
see it too I assume it will be up on the
family YouTube along with this video
that I am recording right now we can see
what the room looks like in that
recording on the right right left left
right side there's a windmill oh I don't
have it in front of me right now I
should on the right side there's a
windmill on the left side there is
something that Marvin does not bother to
look at but we will be looking at so the
question is what do I do
next if I if I were in this room right
now would I I want to go to the thing
that Marvin didn't look at so I'm gonna
go to the right and I think so if I go
to the right god I think I went a little
too far actually
ah dad no well I think actually what
happened is here the problem is that
it's a kind of a branching point I could
stop it could be blocked by the beds or
I could keep going past the bed so the
other side of the room so I could
actually be on either side of the room
right now but either way I guess it
doesn't matter but I'm going to assume
I'm on the thing that I got blocked by
the beds and I if I go up up up up just
keep going up there will be a question
mark that appears that will let me go
and do something if I press X something
will happen and what will happen I think
possibly a text box will open because
that's what happens with the windmill
right I'm gonna press I press X and a
text box appeared with text in it that
is probably cryptic and we don't really
care too much about so we're gonna press
X a bunch of times to get through all
the text but we can look at it later and
there could be a lot of it so be it like
a book and there a lot of stuff I don't
care about part of it or or it's not a
text box and it could be literally
anything else in the world that happens
when you when you press X so the next
thing I can think to do is just press
buttons randomly and chaotically and
hopefully we'll some results so I'm
doing that right now I know if you can
hear that uh
I'm being real thinking you know I'm
thinking I'm being
[Music]
I think I'm definitely it's just that we
can see yeah what are you doing play
this game too much okay
so the windmill isn't there I think I
can so I get blocked by the I do get
blocked by the beds and I go up I think
oh god I could be doing this I shouldn't
be doing this while I'm talking
so anyway well was he so I've seen I've
actually seen recordings that it made of
me
from a year ago and I had not seen that
no recording in the time between so it
was holding onto this thing and it only
decided a year later to playback there
are also recordings that I assume are
stored on the CD or might even be
scripted but in one of the recent videos
this is this is one that went on the
public YouTube
I lost the video I lost it
I had the audio the game had the
recording even there were two parts to
this this session I had both of them and
played them back two different occasions
as demo recordings I got them but okay
so here's the thing those those demo
recordings can be different alright they
can be different from when I was playing
the one so when I caught all those pets
and it showed the text that was
different from what I show up when I was
playing it shared something it happened
to line up right perfectly same number
of text boxes and so forth and also the
music wasn't there in the demo there can
be differences and this was part of what
made it seem reasonable that the door
could be open I'm not saying it wasn't
still nuts so I'm actually going to do
this now so right so I'm assuming that
triangle is back but it could be square
circle
didn't all of them I can actually you
can actually I think you can rotate
these okay so I mean I could have gone
just totally off the rails by this point
I could be anywhere
so it's
five was this room over here and now
attempt six we're going to try to push a
bucket into the other room going back to
this room now again got to make sure
this is aligned exactly right mm it's
okay
and I'm just going to leave it there
and see what happens
you
turn again this is a tempest 22 that's
right I'm talking about that
[Music]
got it
all right now we're in the scary part -
you know one two three four five six
seven
[Music]
Here I am
it deleted my files
[Music]
that's supposed to mean
so what I'm thinking is that this is
either 1995 or or it's 2017
[Music]
second
you
I think
if that was based
off of a conversation
that I had last year on my birthday
[Music]
if it wasn't just a coincidence
then that means I'm
[Music]
getting pranked
but I don't know how that magic trick
works exactly
damn froze
[Music]
I feel very weird
so through Google I asked the Internet
how might one rewrite to a CDR and the
Internet's response to that question was
you idiot hmm idiot
what are you doing some things you can't
rewrite
so I'm in the garage now
Oh
speaking of this
this is the website
for some reason it's in the game on a
computer screen but yeah this is it
and this is the this is the your child
page judging by all the text which I
could read it
Jesus this is a different age and no
idea what's going on anymore what even
is this
[Music]