Hey there.
How's it going?
Yeah, I'm okay. What do you think of that picture?
Yeah, so I,
I, I went up, and I typed  "where is the windmill?",
and that didn't work,
and so, uh,
I tried "where was the windmill?"
and that's how I got the text.
In the picture.
Yeah. Yeah, I looked them up.
The top numbers, I looked them up.
Uh,
you, you're gonna want to look them up yourself.
Yeah, punch 'em in.
Yeah.
I'll wait.
It's a, it's a two.
I know!
I know, me too.
That, that was what, f-- first thought. First thought.
There's not a lot of detail.
Uh, but,
it looks like a stone, right?
Not yet, actually, I wanted to go with you, tomorrow.
Uh, that's why I...
we, yeah.
Friday.
How about that?
Okay. No, I'm gonna sit on it, until then.
I'm, I'm not showing the family until I've seen it myself.
Yeah... well, I don't, I don't,
I don't know, I'm not recording. I stopped it.
Uh, so, what do you think of the bottom numbers?
No, they're different. I wanna hear what you think, first.
Mm, ye-- yeah, yup. Yup.
Yup.
Yeah, we, we would have to find out how big.
Like, we have to find out how big a tile is,
one of the tiles.
Like, if we, if we could figure out how big
one tile is,
in uni--, in, um, like, feet.
Or, uh yeah, meters.
If we could...
what I'm thinking is, if we could measure how far away
the staircase is,
the, the staircase is, from the windmill,
the staircase closest, you know,
the one that's closest to the windmill,
if we could measure how far away that is,
from the windmill,
what I'm wondering,
is, if we could find something there.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, exactly, we could do that.
Uh, it's, uh,
I mean, this is, this,
it's unlikely, this is already pretty...
It's exciting.
This is why I'm not telling the family, because it's exciting. Uh.
Um, but it's unlikely, but it's still, it's still worth a try,
and, what I think, what I'm thinking
we should do,
go and measure the stone on the ground,
compare it to the size of the windmill in the game,
and then we can use that for conversions.
Which, we can do it based on tiles,
how far we can walk in a second, like speed,
whatever, whatever is the easy way to
do what I'm thinking.
Sure.
And, oh, I think it's more, I think it's more likely we
could use real life to find things in the game,
like, the reverse.
Um,
which, we can, we can do that,
and then we don't have to, like, aimlessly walk around to find stuff.
That would be interesting.
Right? If we could take...
That, that's, yup. Yup.
I know, isn't this...
I can probably just measure the stone now, from the,
from the satellite right now, roughly.
Uh, no, they don't know much more than we do now. They didn't...
I don't like talking to them. They intimidate me.
Uh, and I'm sure they wouldn't intimidate you, at all.
Yeah, have they called you?
They haven't called you, right?
I mean, Jill specifically, she hasn't called you?
No, I, I didn't voluntarily mention you.
She asked,
because,
'cause, you know, I'm talking to you in the first few videos.
Right? And so she asked who, who I'm talking to
in the videos, and so I told her, but,
she didn't ask anything else, so I don't think she actually cares.
Yeah.
And, I don't, and you don't have to worry about it, right? 'Cause,
'cause you aren't, you aren't family, so you wouldn't have a room.
That's the thing.
Uh.
I, I didn't mean it that way, just,
you probably don't have a room, that's, that's my only point.
Yeah, no, it's fine.
Uh, no, you don't want her calling you anyway.
Like, you won't be able,
you won't be able to escape, that's the thing,
if she were to start... yeah.
And I should start taking you up on that offer.
Hey, I need your genius.
I need your, um...
Trying to
navigate here.
Yeah, I need your, I need your puzzle genius.
No, no, you're,
you're a genius.
Wait, let me,
let me get there before I start talking about this.
You sure?
Yeah. You weren't in the middle of something, were you?
I can let you go.
Good, well, okay, so,
I was expecting the cage puzzle to lead into something else,
Uh, but there's really nothing here
left.
Yeah. Um.
The Tiara character is gone, now.
Yeah, completely, like, you look over on the other side,
and now there's noth-- there was, there was,
like, the, the Tiara character was there,
and then I left, and then the next time I came back,
they were gone.
What do you mean, "of course"?
Give me a second to verify that logic.
[Paul moving around in seat]
[thump]
What?
Why would I be in a car?
I'm playing Petscop.
Why would I be playing Petscop in a car?
[laughs] The fuck?
That was just my door.
Front door.
Doesn't make any sense.
No, no, it was, that was my door.
I was stretching.
[thump]
Hey, what the fuck?
Uhhhh.
I just got hit by a car.
I walked on the... so, the road,
where the cars pass by, and they never hit me?
I just walked on that road, and a car hit me.
And I disappeared.
Uh, ye... shit.
Uh, no I, fuck, need to start -- forgot to start the recording.
They won't like that.
So I, I missed that, I did not, was not able to
capture that, I wonder if I can
get that to happen... fuck.
Whoa.
Hey.
You there?
Belle, you there?
Hello?
Shit.
What are you doing there?
Why are you just standing there?
What the fuck?
[Paul drops controller]
You want me to do something?
Come on, what do you want?
I know you're trying to say something to me.
What do you want?
What?
[Paul moving in seat]
[Paul smacks something] What?
[quiet thump]
[background music: "school" ♪]
[background music: "counselor" ♪]
[background music: "bottom" ♪]
[music volume increasing]