[Applause]
looks like we finally made some progress
I think well just to figure out what to
do with it you know it probably has to
do it this thing than the tool in the
room yeah try to get that yeah these two
are definitely blocking it
that means
[Applause]
all right so it comes up if I oh wow
okay
[Applause]
okay there's a new file you might might
have occurred to you as it occurred to
me that these rooms are but in this room
and the house our counterparts if they
both have this bucket and they're shaped
similarly so I thought I would try out
what we did before yeah and it worked
God I'm not gonna be able to get this
sewer okay hmm good eye this is working
out pretty well and I'm feeling some
doubt because this seems way too
small but I should not have felt out I
just
what we finally
[Music]